// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What does SQL stand for?",
    answer: "Structured Query Language",
    options: [
      "Strong Question Language",
      "Structured Question Language",
      "Structured Query Language",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which SQL statement is used to update data in a database?",
    answer: "UPDATE",
    options: [
      "UPDATE",
      "MODIFY",
      "SAVE",
      "SAVE AS"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which SQL statement is used to insert new data in a database?",
    answer: "INSERT INTO",
    options: [
      "ADD RECORD",
      "INSERT NEW",
      "ADD NEW",
      "INSERT INTO"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "With SQL, how do you select all the columns from a table named 'Persons'?",
    answer: "SELECT * FROM Persons",
    options: [
      "SELECT [all] FROM Persons",
      "SELECT * FROM Persons",
      "SELECT *.Persons",
      "SELECT Persons"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "With SQL, how do you select a column named 'FirstName' from a table named 'Persons'?",
    answer: "SELECT FirstName FROM Persons",
    options: [
      "SELECT Persons.FirstName",
      "SELECT FirstName FROM Persons",
      "EXTRACT FirstName FROM Persons",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which SQL keyword is used to sort the result-set?",
    answer: "ORDER BY",
    options: [
      "SORT",
      "ORDER",
      "SORT BY",
      "ORDER BY"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the most common type of join?",
    answer: "INNER JOIN",
    options: [
      "INNER JOIN",
      "INSIDE JOIN",
      "JOINED TABLE",
      "JOINED"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which operator is used to select values within a range?",
    answer: "BETWEEN",
    options: [
      "RANGE",
      "WITHIN",
      "BETWEEN",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which operator is used to search for a specified pattern in a column?",
    answer: "LIKE",
    options: [
      "GET",
      "LIKE",
      "FROM",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which SQL statement is used to create a database table called 'Customers'?",
    answer: "CREATE TABLE Customers",
    options: [
      "CREATE TABLE Customers",
      "CREATE DB Customers",
      "CREATE DATABASE TABLE Customers",
      "CREATE DATABASE TAB Customers"
    ]
  },
];